bracbank.com 2018-11-04

# BRAC Bank Limited Mobile Internet Banking Application Privacy Policy

BRAC Bank Limited Mobile Internet Banking Application Privacy Policy
This Mobile Internet Banking Application Privacy Policy (“Policy”) applies to users of Mobile
Internet Banking Application (“App.”) through BRAC Bank Limited. The term “BBL”, “Bank” or “we”,
“us” or “our(s)” in the mobile banking application we own and control and in this Policy refers to
BRAC Bank Limited.
BRAC Bank Limited is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its customers and has taken
all necessary and reasonable measures to safeguard the confidentiality of any information that is
transmitted through its Mobile Internet Banking Application. This online privacy policy explains
how we collect, share, use and protect information when you visit or use this Mobile Internet
Banking Application.
Through the Mobile Internet Banking Application, you may use your Eligible Mobile Device to view
balances and recent transactions for each of your Accounts; make transfers of funds; and access
additional services that may be available through a Mobile Application.
As you review this Mobile Privacy Policy, here are a few general principles to keep in mind:
    1. Agreement to Policy
        By downloading BRAC Bank Mobile Internet Banking App. on your mobile device, you
        confirm your affirmative consent to all the terms of this Policy detailed below and comply
        with any other security procedures that we may establish from time to time.
    2. Gathering, Using and Sharing: Information that we collect
        Information that we may collect about you through mobile banking includes information
        that you voluntarily disclose, such as your name, address, phone number, email address
        and other contact information, along with transaction information, information resulting
        from your mobile activity and your location information. We may also gather additional
        information associated with your mobile device through cookies and other technologies as
        described below.
    3. Usage and Other Information
        In addition to the personal information described above, we may collect certain
        information about your use of our online services. For example, we may capture the IP
        address of the device you use to connect to the online service, the type of operating
        system and browser you use, and information about the site you came from, the parts of
        our online service you access, and the site you visit next. We may also use cookies, web
        beacons or other technologies to collect and store other information about your visit to, or
        use of, our online services. In addition, we may later associate the usage and other
        information we collect online with personal information about you.
    4. BRAC Bank Mobile Internet Banking Service
        For your convenience, BRAC Bank offers you the ability to access some of our products
        and services through mobile banking applications. When you interact with us through
        BRAC Bank Mobile Internet Banking App., we may collect information such as unique
        device identifiers for your mobile device, your screen resolution and other device settings,

   information about your location, and analytical information about how you use your
   mobile device.
5. Location Tracking
   There may be certain information transmitted to us regarding your location when you
   request information through applications on your mobile device, such as your physical
   location while accessing the App. Location Data we collect from your mobile device will
   assist us in mitigating against any potential breaches or unauthorized access to customer
   information.
6. Use of Information
    We use the information discussed above in a number of ways, such as:
        Processing applications and transactions.
        Verifying your identity (such as when you access your account information).
        Preventing fraud and enhancing the security of your account or our online services.
        Responding to your requests and communicating with you.
        Complying with and enforcing applicable legal requirements, relevant industry
           standards, contractual obligations and our policies.
7. Disclosure of Information
   We may share the information that we collect from and about you as well as information
   about your Accounts or the transactions you make, with our affiliates within BRAC Bank,
   with credit reference agencies and with any third parties with whom we have signed Non-
   Disclosure Agreements. However, we will disclose information to third parties about your
   account or the transactions you make, and you authorize us to do so, ONLY in the
   following situations:
        In order to comply with the requirements of the law or with court orders.
        In order to address, rectify, ameliorate or mitigate fraud, security or technical
           issues.
        With our trusted service providers (when required) who work on our behalf and do
           not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have
           agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this Privacy Policy.
8. Data Retention
           Our operational systems will store user-provided data for as long as you use the
           related feature of the Mobile Application. Please note that some or all of the user-
           provided data may be required in order for the Mobile Internet Banking
           Application to function properly, and we may be required by law to retain certain
           information. If you close your profile established for Mobile Internet Banking, we
           will retain certain data for a reasonable time to facilitate any request to reopen
           your profile.
9. Updating Your Information
   You may be able to review and update your account information though the App.

10. Security Measures
         Protecting the confidentiality of your information is very important to us. We have
            established appropriate physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect
            information we collect from or about our users. For example, we limit access to this
            information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that
            information in order to operate, develop or improve our Mobile Application. These
            safeguards are regularly reviewed to protect against unauthorized access,
            disclosure and improper use of your information and to maintain the accuracy and
            integrity of that information.
         User IDs and Passcodes are used to help safeguard against unauthorized access to
            your information through the Mobile Banking Application or Mobile Web. As
            always, we strongly encourage you to assist us in that effort by not sharing your
            BRAC Bank Mobile or Internet Banking User ID and Passcodes with anyone.
         We take reasonable security measures to help protect your information, both
            during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of electronic
            transmission or method of electronic storage is 100% secure.
11. Consent to Transfer
    If you are located outside of the Bangladesh, please be aware that information we collect
    through the App will be transferred to and processed in Bangladesh. By using the App or
    providing us with any information, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to this
    transfer, processing and storage of your information in Bangladesh.
12. Children's Privacy
    We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13
    without parental consent. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide
    personally identifiable information of any kind.
13. Questions and Concerns
    If you have any questions about this Policy or our privacy practices, please contact our
    24/7 call center number at 16221 OR email us at enquiry@bracbank.com
14. Policy Updates and Effective Date
    This Policy is subject to change and any changes to this Policy will become effective when
    posted on this application. Your use of the application following these changes means you
    accept the revised Policy.
